Me wo aketa kikkake wa
Kokoro saku joukei
Hirari hirari yubi no sukima kara
Mietekuru shinjitsu wo nirame
Kizukareta no wa, rakuen?
Massakasama ochite
Aa tatoe kouya demo
Hitori de ikiru to oritachimashou
Ikanakucha
Koko ni aru hana wa ima eien nare to
Gokujou no chihedo wo haite watashi ga ueta mono
Kono koe de ashi de te de watashi no mama mogaku hodo ni
Doushiyou mo nai sekai ga itoshii
Tadoritsuku wa kanarazu
Musekaeru hodo no yume
FILE: Flower Garden Lily
You passed the enrollment exam.
Congratulations on getting accepted.
I'm... I'm going to work hard
and become a great spy!
Make sure that you do.
We're expecting great things out of you.
Thank you, ma'am!
She was so young.
I don't think we've accepted a student that young
since Flower Garden.
That jazz selection brings us right into our news from the States.
It's been half a year.
I doubt a washout like her could have survived that long.
That jazz selection brings us right into our news from the States.
For the last few days, the Mitario tabloids have been abuzz
with speculation about their local villain.
They call her Lillian the Devil,
but her real name is Lillian Hepburn.
She's been connected to seventy-six suspicious deaths
and was shot to death after a standoff with the police,
Hey, Lillian, you're the talk of the town.
but the shocking part is that by day,
Thanks for noticing, Sybilla!
she worked as a normal waitress
at Westport Building's ground floor burger joint.
At long last, my era's finally arrived!
Mysteries abound about who this woman really was,
and as speculation continues flying,
I see you've decided to accept the inevitable.
some articles have even gone so far as to theorize
Check out the mugshot.
that Lillian is secretly still alive...
That doesn't look anything like her.
It's a misdirection tactic.
Teach and the United States's intelligence agency
intentionally spread it as misinformation.
I think it's cool how sinister she looks, yo.
Right?
When my story gets made into a movie,
I bet they'll get a big-name actress to play me!
You'd think I'd be used to it by now,
but shit just rolls off her back, huh?
It really does.
It's one of her most admirable qualities.
She seems fine, but it's the other
absentee I'm worried about.
I haven't seen her leave her room in days.
Is she still asleep?
Huh?
Thea!
This is for you.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Hey, Thea, you'll never guess what they were
just saying on the radio about-
Thea?
Hmm...
You can't really blame her.
She went through a lot in Mitario.
I wonder if I have anything with
an aroma that would help her relax...
What's this?
"Klaus loves you."
Klaus loves you
"Klaus covets you"?
No, that isn't it either.
After I found that key,
I started looking for the keyhole it went with.
Eventually...
There!
Ms. Hearth...
When you passed away six months ago,
you predicted that Teach would bring me to Mitario.
Inferno had fallen,
so with his teammates gone,
Teach was bound to build a new team.
That much makes sense.
You could definitely have predicted as much
back when you were still alive.
But how could you have known that
I was one of the people he would recruit?
Are you saying that filling in this blank
will help me understand that?
Yeeeeep!
Teach is in love with me?
There's no way.
Unless... Wait a sec!
Back in Mitario...
Looks like you're out of tricks.
Teach...
That was magnificent, Lily.
You fought well.
Go ahead and rest for a bit.
Thinking back now, that was
totally a bridal carry he did.
Could Teach actually be in love with me?
Big Sis Lily?
What happened?
N-nothing!
Nothing happened!
I smell something interesting afoot, yo.
Me too.
What's this?
Looks shifty.
Don't look at it!
Well, uh, long story short!
That's what's going on!
You'll understand everything once you read it!
"Klaus..."
"...loves you"?
Who was this meant for?
I mean...
we're the ones Lily gave it to, right?
Yeep!
So, Teach is in love with me?
Pretty sure it's just some nasty misinformation, yo.
Yeeeep!
I should really get this room fixed already.
What should I do?
Should I just bite the bullet and ask Teach directly?
What now?
Yeeeeeeeeeeep!
Hey, Annette, Lily and Erna are acting weird.
You have any idea what's going on?
I've got the cause right here, yo.
This is for you, Sis.
Thanks.
Once you read it, you'll understand everything.
What even is this?
Is it addressed to me?
This is stupid.
What should we make for dinner tonight?
How's hamburgers sound?
That radio report got me thinkin' about 'em.
Ooh, that's a good idea.
Anyone up for a game?
Yeep.
I'm not feelin' it right now.
Me neither.
Could Teach...
...really feel that way about me?
What do I do? How the hell...
...am I supposed to break this to the others?
I just bought up a gazillion cakes!
Let's make some tea,
and I'll explain while we're eating.
I've got something really important to tell you all!
What kinda somethin'?
A big something!
About Teach!
Ah, there you all are.
I have something I wanted to ask you.
N-no way, Teach, you wouldn't!
You're not about to ask me out
in front of everyone, are you?!
FILE: Flower Garden Lily
Some contractors are going to be arriving
this evening to fix up Lily's room.
These are special spy repairmen.
I imagine this won't be the last time
we need their services,
so I was wondering if one of you
would join me in welcoming them.
J-just one of us?!
Alone with you?!
Well, there's no need for all of you to
expose your faces to them.
You're the leader, Lily,
so you're in charge of figuring it out.
Wh-who, me?!
Yes, you. Thanks.
What was going on there?
All of them were acting strangely.
T-Teach, do you hear what you're saying?
That would make it our very first
l-lovey-dovey joint op!
By the way, where're Grete and Thea?
Oh, I don't know.
I think they took off for somewhere.
Th-that's right!
It's not like I actually want to start dating Teach.
If anything, I'd much rather help Grete
have her love come to fruition!
And plus, I'm also Lamplight's leader.
I need to put this whole situation to rest
before Grete gets back!
I've made up my mind!
Can I ask everyone's advice about something?
Advice? What kinda advice?
I-it's about love!
I want to go tell Teach about how
I really feel about him!
That's right.
I need to make sure he knows I'm not interested!
I need to protect Grete.
I need to protect our team unity!
That's a bad call, Lily.
You're gonna get hurt.
After all, I'm the one...
I'm the one...
...he's really in love with!
I'm terribly sorry.
I was afraid that you were trying
to seduce the boss in earnest, Master.
I see...
So? Where is it we're going, Grete?
There's someone I want you to meet.
That note of yours is quite the puzzle.
I suspect we'll need more information
if we want to solve it.
There's a woman who might have some answers
about the boss and Inferno.
Grete, is this...
It is.
Congratulations on being released,
Olivia.
What're you doing here, you crazy bitch?
I have something I wanted to ask you.
I need information about my boss's past.
Would you be so kind as to tell me the intelligence
that got leaked to the Galgad Empire?
And why would I do that?
I see no reason to tell you a thing.
Roland passed away over in Mitario.
That button is from the shirt he was wearing.
It's the only memento he left behind.
Tell me one thing, Bonfire.
Do you think I ever could have become your rival?
Not in a million years.
Teach...
Did you expect me to console you?
You're going to die without having achieved
a single one of your goals.
Considering how many innocent lives you've taken,
it's a fitting way for you to go.
That said,
I would say you've earned yourself the right
to have us give you a proper sendoff.
Hey, I'll take it.
It only lasted for a single moment,
and maybe it was all just a sick joke,
but it was kind of nice getting to
fight by your side back there.
Thea, thank you for saving me.
Roland...
You wanted information about Bonfire, was it?
Well, there's not much I actually know.
All Roland told me was to avoid
fighting him no matter what,
and to call for help the moment I ran into him.
That, and he gave me a photo and a name.
I see.
May I ask what that name was?
There were a couple he told me:
Bonfire... The Dust King...
Ax... Lone... Practical...
That and Crowbar were all of them, I think.
That's all I can really tell you.
That's enough chatting.
Let's go.
Olivia only has at most half a year left to live.
Before they release her at the airport,
they're going to secretly dose her with a drug.
Shortly after she arrives back in her homeland,
her mind will start to become muddled.
She'll spread all sorts of incomprehensible
gibberish before ultimately perishing.
Does she know?
I can't imagine they would tell her
something like that.
This time it really is goodbye, Olivia.
There's something I realized after
hearing Olivia's description.
One of the names she listed was Crowbar.
You must have already met the boss seven years ago.
During the rescue, he was the one who
killed your kidnappers with a crowbar.
But he's never shown me the slightest sign
that that's the case!
You figured something out, didn't you, Grete?
Please, just give it to me straight.
Whatever it is, that must have been
Ms. Hearth wanted me to realize.
In that case, well...
Hearth took care of you on her own
after the rescue, correct?
Yeah...
And all of the dead kidnappers were male, right?
That's right.
A group of men captured and locked me up-
No...
How could I not remember something like that?
The trauma likely made your memories fuzzy.
Young as he was at the time, the boss was still male,
so Hearth must have made him leave the area.
It makes sense why he never told you what happened.
You know...
People assume that assault victims like you
will develop androphobia...
...but there are cases of people who abandon their
inhibitions in order to overwrite their trauma.
Ms. Hearth guided me down the
path to becoming a spy
in order to help me avoid developing a sex addiction.
That's what you're saying, right?
That's right.
And the boss knew that that was her plan,
so seven years later when he was putting together
Lamplight, he chose you for the team.
That's how Ms. Hearth was able to predict
that I would end up in Mitario.
She knew that Teach's connection to me
would lead him to bring me there.
That belief inspired her to spread the rumor
about the black-haired hero.
So, that's the full truth.
"Klaus saved you."
That's what the message was telling me.
She wanted to help me face my past.
Thea...
Ms. Hearth...
I wish I could have talked with you again.
Grete...
Sometimes, it feels like life has
too many downs and not enough ups.
It does, yes.
We're back.
What even HAPPENED here?!
I finally caught her.
I filmed the whole thing, yo!
It was just as funny as I hoped it would be.
Maybe funnier!
At the time, I felt like I had to keep
Lily from asking Teach out,
even if that meant stopping her by force.
Yeah, same, after all...
...I didn't want to see Big Sis Lily ask Teach out
only to end up with her feelings hurt!
Wh-what are you three talking about?
That doesn't make sense!
Don't you know that I'm the one Teach is in love with?!
It all started 'cuz of this, yo!
What is this?
Oh, it's the note I wrote.
I must have dropped it somewhere.
Say WHAT?!
So, that bit about Teach being in love with me...
Was a misunderstanding.
All of it was!
Who was the first one to pick it up?
I would say that they're the main culprit here.
I-I was acting in my capacity as team leader!
I was trying to protect the team!
Oh, thank you, Lily.
I was feeling down, but you cheered me right up.
I'd like to thank you too, Lily.
Hey, don't go hogging all
the catharsis for yourselves!
I demand satisfaction!
Now that I think about it,
she mentioned this a lot back when she was still alive.
No matter how awash in pain the world gets,
never let it break you, Klaus.
You mustn't forget to put smiles on people's faces.
Thank you for reminding me of that, Lily.
I can see that I made the right call
back when I appointed you as team leader.
Looks like you're doing all right for yourself,
Flower Garden.
Back when I heard that a washout like you
would be joining a team that
specialized in Impossible Missions,
I figured it would be, well, impossible.
But clearly, I was wrong.
You've found a place where you belong.
A flower garden where you can bloom freely.
Stop laughing at me, dammit!
In case you forgot, I'm your leader!
I'm about to get mad here.
I'm gonna be angrier than angry!
The repairs are all finished,
so there's something I wanted to tell you again.
It's about what I mentioned before we left for Mitario.
How if you completed the mission,
you would all graduate.
Well, congratulations.
You completed the mission with flying colors.
Consider yourselves graduates.
I've got a question.
Actually, it's a question from all of us.
Wouldn't the logical thing be
to take the repaired room,
the one that used to belong to Hearth,
and have you inherit it, Teach?
What?
I concur.
Me too.
Ditto.
M-me too!
So do I.
I agree with the others, yo!
What do you say, Boss?
We all feel the same way.
I say, no.
And don't call me Boss.
That doesn't seem right.
By this point, you're well and truly our boss, Boss.
C'mon, what's the harm?
We're all graduatin',
so you should go ahead and graduate, too.
Move on from that wishy-washy position of yours.
So, you're saying we need to bring
the team to its next stage?
We do have the Serpent situation to consider.
Roland!
Screw off, you freak.
I can't believe you seriously captured Purple Ant alive.
You're really making a nuisance of yourself, Bonfire.
For Serpent, that is.
What are you people trying to achieve?
You're not just some random team
of Imperial loyalists.
What makes you think that?
My mentor never would have joined you if you were.
Well, if I had to put it into words...
we're trying to balance the scales.
You're right.
I am Lamplight's boss.
And to me, you all are...
No matter what Serpent's goal is,
it's certain to be something that will
shake the world to its core.
It's up to us, Lamplight, to stop them.
Are you ready?
Yes, sir!
Magnificent.